<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/demo_jll/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/demo_jll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-03-13T15:40:11+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/demo_jll/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/demo_jll/2024/03/12/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll" /><published>2024-03-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-03-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/demo_jll/2024/03/12/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/demo_jll/2024/03/12/welcome-to-jekyll.html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to our new Jekyll-powered blog! In this post, we’ll share some thoughts and tips about using Jekyll for creating websites.</p>

<h3 id="why-choose-jekyll">Why Choose Jekyll?</h3>

<p>Jekyll is a fantastic tool for building websites for several reasons:</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Simplicity</strong>: Jekyll allows you to focus on your content without worrying about complex setups.</li>
  <li><strong>Flexibility</strong>: With Jekyll’s templating system and plugins, you can create virtually any type of website.</li>
  <li><strong>Speed</strong>: Since Jekyll generates static HTML files, your website will load quickly, improving user experience and SEO.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="getting-started">Getting Started</h3>

<p>To get started with Jekyll, follow these steps:</p>

<ol>
  <li>Install Jekyll and Bundler using RubyGems: <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">gem install jekyll bundler</code>.</li>
  <li>Create a new Jekyll site: <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">jekyll new my-site</code>.</li>
  <li>Navigate to the newly created directory: <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">cd my-site</code>.</li>
  <li>Serve your site locally: <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">bundle exec jekyll serve</code>.</li>
  <li>Customize your site’s layout, content, and styling according to your needs.</li>
</ol>

<h3 id="conclusion">Conclusion</h3>

<p>We’re excited to embark on this journey with Jekyll, and we hope you find our future posts helpful and inspiring. Stay tuned for more tips, tutorials, and insights into the world of web development with Jekyll!</p>]]></content><author><name>John Doe</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our new Jekyll-powered blog! In this post, we’ll share some thoughts and tips about using Jekyll for creating websites.]]></summary></entry></feed>